Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1975-1989; Accession 1990-A-032
  - Public Broadcasting Service, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 638)
  - Business Office Expense Reports, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 639)
  - Lloyd Richards: Moving Expenses, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 640)
  - Richards, Lloyd: Expenses: NY Office for Yale, 1979-1986 (Box 13, Folder 641)
  - Personal Expenses, 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 642)
  - Yale Expenses, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 643 - 644)
  - London, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 645 - 646)
  - Quebec, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 647)
  - Sweden, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 648)
  - Trip to Russia, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 649)
  - International Trade Institute: Poland, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 650)
  - Bulgaria International Trade Institute trip, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 651)
  - Dean's office repairs, etc., 1979-1985 (Box 14, Folder 652)
  - Richards, L. Personal Correspondences, 1979-1986 (Box 14, Folder 653 - 654)
  - Richards, L. Photos, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 655)
  - Lloyd Richards: Personal Photos, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 656)
  - Recommendations: Richards, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 657)
  - Richards L. Publicity: General, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 658)
  - Recommendations, 1981-1986 (Box 14, Folder 659 - 663)
- Records of the Yale School of Drama, circa 1971-1999; Accession 2001-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2034
  - [Returned to office] (Box 1)
  - Budget and Financial 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Audience Services: 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Design 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Production
    - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cabaret
    - Notes-Artistic Statements-Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Financial, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Summer Cabaret (Box 2, Folder 9 - 10)
  - Bankruptcy Proceeding with:
    - Cornucopia Distributor (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - CHARGIT (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gift and Grants
    - General Grants and Gifts, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Project Eli (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 9th Square Project (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Calvin Trillin Benefit (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Lloyd Richard's Benefit-Chair (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Stage Management, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Theatre Magazine, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Drama Alumni Association, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - University Safety Committee
    - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Escort Service
    - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Log Books and Policies (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Staff Meetings
    - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Leadership seminar (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - FOCUS (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Management Articles (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Memos (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Computers Articles and Notes (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Computer Courses (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Computer-Hardware and Software (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Old Systems (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - YSD-YRT General Manager's Files
    - Personnel Issues (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - YST-YRT Production Calendars, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Drop Repertory Show (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Barbara (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Contact Sheet (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Payne Whitney Gym Contract (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - New Haven Artist's Theatre (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Theatre Management Files
  - Administration Program (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Position Descriptions (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Pending Job Audits (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Accounting Test (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Student Files
  - Development (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Reference (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Yale Theatre Circle (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Productions
    - General Production Issues, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Drama 50's, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Drama 101's, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - "Twelfth Night" (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - "Good Person of Setzuan" (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - "Nabo: The Black Man Who Made The Angels Wait" (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - "Hamlet" (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - "Richard III" (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - "Cobb" (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - "Cobb" (Rep. Financial) (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - "Titus" (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Verse Project--"King John" and "As You Like It"
      - Sam Waterston (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - "St. Carmen of the Main" (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - "Pericles" (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Unlabeled folder (USA--LORT Contract?) (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Drama 101's, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Drama 50's, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - "Mississippi Nude" (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - "Hamlet Machine" (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - "Hamlet" (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Verse Project (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Drama 101's, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Drama 50's, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - "Cherry Orchard" (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - "Three Sisters" (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - "Shadows" (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - "Macbeth" (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - "American Rickshaw" (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - "Book and Canon" (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - "American Beech" (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - "Four Saint in Three Acts" (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - "Translations" (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - "Soon" (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - "Everything in the Garden" (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - "There are Crimes and Crimes" (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - "A Night at the Theatre" (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - "The Sinking of the Titanic" (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - "Resistible Rise" (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - "Becoming Legends" (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - "The Alchemist" (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - "Only the Brave are Brave" (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - "Chute Roosters" (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - "The Revenger's Tragedy" (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Drama 50's, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Business Office
    - 1989-1990 Budget
      - Version 1.02 (Box 3, Folder 109)
      - Version 1.03 (Box 3, Folder 110)
      - Version 1.04 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Yale Repertory Budgets and Actuals, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Misc. (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Yale Repertory October Projections, 1991 October (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Yale Repertory Projections, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Survey Entered (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - L.O.R.T. Survey (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Press Release: Yale Repertory Theatre, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - "Ivonov" Opening Night Party (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Unlabeled folder (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Summer Compensation, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Box Office
    - Five Play Stubs (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Department Worksheets, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Subscription Campaign, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Subscription Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Group Sales, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - House Manager Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Single Ticket Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Receipts, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - New Marketing (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Seating Floor Plan University Theatre (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Marketing
      - News Letters (Box 4, Folder 132)
      - Press Releases (Box 4, Folder 133)
      - Art Work and Originals, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre Student Comps. (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Cast Lists (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Short Bios (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - New Haven Audition, 1987 September 27 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Casting Directors (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Simon and Kumin
    - Contract (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Casting (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Various (Box 4, Folder 142 - 143)
    - Cast Lists (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Students--Non Professionals (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Casting (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Long Range Plan--Financial (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Production, 1988-1989
    - Season General Information (Box 4, Folder 150)
      - Rotations (Box 4, Folder 151)
      - Company Management (Box 4, Folder 152)
      - Memos In (Box 4, Folder 153)
      - Memo Out (Box 4, Folder 154)
      - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 155)
      - Script Sign Out Sheets (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - "Tempest" (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - "Faustus" (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - "Galileo" (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Winterfest Memo (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - "Joe Turner" (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - "Medea" (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - "The Seagull" (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Drama 50's Memos (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Drama 101's
      - General, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 165)
      - Manual (Box 4, Folder 166)
      - Budgets (Box 4, Folder 167)
      - Budget Materials (Box 4, Folder 168)
      - Program Originals (Box 4, Folder 169)
      - Memos (Box 4, Folder 170)
      - Projects (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - "The Warrior Ant"
      - General Manager Laurel Ann Wilson (Box 4, Folder 172)
      - Warrior Ant (Box 4, Folder 173)
      - Running Crew and Load in Labor (Box 4, Folder 174)
      - Company Manager Service Agreement (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - The Prompter
    - 1988 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Performance Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Budget Book, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Year End and Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Budget, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 182 - 183)
  - General Accounting, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Admin D. Job Description (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - Impact Management (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Memos In (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Blank Quick Copy Forms (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Blank Expense Reports Forms (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Expense Reports Blank Forms (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Fire Safety Signs (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Budget Worksheets
    - 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Inventory, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 196 - 197)
  - Space Committee (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Space Utilization (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - School Security Committee (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Props Warehouse (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Salary Worksheets
    - 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Budget Book, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - University IRS Payroll Tax Audit, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Scholarships and Grants (Box 5)
    - Scholarships, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Academic Needs Report (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Budgets for Grants, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - College Work Study Grant, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 209 - 210)
    - Scholarship Forms, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Winterfest
    - Budget (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Gifts (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Summer Programs (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - General Manager's Files
    - Buzz Ward (Box 5, Folder 216 - 217)
    - Unidentified, loose financial records (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - LORT--Other USA contract (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - LORT supplemental Agreement (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - LORT--SSDC contract (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - TDandP contract (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Business Office
    - Business Manager Job Information (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Honoraria, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 234 - 235)
    - Gifts and Grants, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 236 - 237)
    - Institutional Development, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Budget Analysis, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Work Study Reorganization (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - Correspondence--General and Incoming (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Long Term Projection (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Budget 3 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Endowment Papers (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - February Provost Submission (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Student Labor (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Budget, preliminary, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Closing -- Potential Problems (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Business Manager Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - University Budget Monitoring and Business Manager Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - Financial Analysis by Department (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - March Projection (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - December Projection (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - October Projection, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - End of The Year Closeout (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Connecticut, State of Higher Education Survey, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - Key Authorization Form, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Loose budget materials, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Budget Binder
    - Budget Final (Box 7)
    - Unlabeled divider (Box 7)
    - Dean (Box 7)
    - Managing Director (Box 7)
    - Associate Dean (Box 7)
    - Production Manager (Box 7)
    - Director Audience Services (Box 7)
    - Student Labor (Box 7)
    - Assistant Business Manager (Box 7)
    - Financial Aid Officer (Box 7)
    - Associate Managing Director (Box 7)
    - Company Manager (Box 7)
    - Director Inst. and Development (Box 7)
    - Operations Manager (Box 7)
    - Cabaret (Box 7)
  - Memberships--Polices and Procedures Originals, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Scholarships--General (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Business Office
    - Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - Budget: 2ndQuarter Projections, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - Budget: 3rdQuarter Projections, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - Abbyload (Later Changed by 74K), 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Advertising Campaign, Jeff Provost Proposal, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Concessions Project, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Audition Tour, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Budget Papers for General Information, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - Budget Provost Communications, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - End of the Year, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - Budget, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - Yale University Financial Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - 1995 Jun (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Budget Preparation Papers, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - Honoraria, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - 1996 Close (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Annual Report, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Budget: General, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - 1stQuarter Monitoring, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Salary Plan M and P, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Promotions (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Networking Computers - Internet, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Educational Programs (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Business Office
    - Yale Repertory Theatre Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Budget: Supervisor Worksheets, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - Budget Version 1.06, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Annual Report
    - 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Loose budget materials (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - 52ndStreet project (Box 8, Folder 295 - 296)
  - Dwight Edgewood (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Theatre Communications Group Survey
  - Salary Survey
    - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - 1994 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - 1993 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Results, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Fall 1993 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Fall 1992 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - 1990 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - 1989 (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Yearly General Ledger for Drama Productions, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Grants
    - NEA: Magazine, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - State of Connecticut Commission on the Arts Grant
      - 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 317)
      - Application, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 318)
      - Grant # 780A-57921, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 319)
      - Midyear Report, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 320)
      - Final Report, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - NEA Grant Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - NEA Grant 130,000 #44747, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Rockefeller Grant, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - NEA Training Award Letter, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - NEA Training Application, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts
    - Final Report of Grant Expenditures, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Final Report, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Application, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - Final Report, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - Application and Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Final Report of Grant Expenditures, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Application and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Final Report of Grant Expenditures, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Midyear Report and Semi-Annual Budget Status, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 340)
    - Application BCR Year I, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 341)
    - Final Report BCR Year I, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 342)
    - Semi-Annual Budget Status Report BCR Year I, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Award Letter and Contract BCR Year I, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Correspondence BCR Year I, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Arts Endowment Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Application Year II, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Final Report BCR Year II, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - Semi-Annual Budget Status Report BCR Year II, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - Award Letter and Contract BCR Year II, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Correspondence BCR Year II, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - Three Year, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 353)
    - One Year Application, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 354)
    - 1987 Mar (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - Letters of Award, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 356)
    - Organizational Review and Multi-Year Funding (Box 9, Folder 357)
    - Letter of Intent Three Year Grant, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 358)
    - Three Year, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 359)
    - A.D.A. Requirements Grant (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities
    - Grant Theatre Translation, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 361)
    - Teatr Award Letter (Box 9, Folder 362)
    - Teatr Final Report (Box 9, Folder 363)
    - Audit Report (Box 9, Folder 364)
    - Basic Research (Box 9, Folder 365)
    - 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 366)
    - Grant Proposal Rejected, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 367)
    - NEH-USIA: Lubimov (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities and Richard Shields Endowment
    - 1976-1977 and Extension (Box 9, Folder 369)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - Original Proposal, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 372)
    - Open Dialog (Box 9, Folder 373)
    - Drama Scholarship Fund (Box 9, Folder 375)
    - Griswold Grants (Box 9, Folder 379)
    - Drama Alumni Fund (Box 9, Folder 385)
    - ASCAP-Cole Porter Prize (Box 9, Folder 386)
    - Unidentified folder (Box 9, Folder 387)
    - Bradley Fellows (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - Unidentified folder (Box 9, Folder 390)
    - FDTN--"Piano Lesson" (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Restricted gifts 65300 misc. (Box 9, Folder 392)
  - Yale School of Drama -Yale Repertory Theatre Three Year Plan, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 394)
  - Ford Grants
    - Matching Grant, 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - Grant, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - 1983-1989 (Box 10, Folder 398)
    - Minority Enrollment Statistics (Box 10, Folder 399)
    - Recruitment Reports (Box 10, Folder 400)
  - Minority Enrollment (Box 10, Folder 401)
    - GRE locator Service, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 402)
    - Mailing List, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Mellon Foundation
    - 1977-1990 (Box 10, Folder 417)
    - Grant, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 418)
    - Grant, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 419)
  - Columbia Pictures Grant (Box 10, Folder 420)
  - Corporate Campaign (Box 10, Folder 421)
  - Box Office Reports Summaries, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 422)
  - Development Office, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 423 - 424)
  - Budget
    - 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 426)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute: Development Office Planning Book, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 427)
  - The Goodman Theatre: Suggested Development Plan, Annual Campaign, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 428)
  - Box Office Reports: Summaries, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 429)
  - State Grants
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts Lobbying:, 1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 430 - 431)
    - Earnest Connecticut Legislators Evening, 1986 April 4 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - "White Paper" for Support (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Connecticut Arts Endowment Fund (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts Hearings: (James Earl Jones), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - Connecticut Arts Endowment Fund (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - Grant--Key (Box 11, Folder 437)
  - National Endowment for the Arts
    - Artistic Associates
      - Athol Fugard, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 440)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    - Literature Grant NEA, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    - Large Theatre Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - Resident Playwright, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 444)
    - Design Arts Application, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Final Report Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - Challenge Grant (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - Training Grants
      - Application, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 448)
      - Revised Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 449)
      - Guidelines, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 450)
      - Contract, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 451)
      - Award, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 452)
      - Application, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 453)
      - Revised Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 454)
      - Guidelines, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 455)
      - Contract, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 456)
      - Award, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 457)
      - Application, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 458)
      - Revised Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 459)
      - Guidelines, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 460)
      - Contract, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 461)
      - Award, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 462)
      - Final Report, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 463)
      - Application, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 464)
      - Training Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 465)
      - Revised Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 466)
      - Award, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 467)
      - Final Report, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 468)
      - Letter of Intent, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 469)
      - Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 470)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 471)
      - Award Letters, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 472)
      - Final Report, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 473)
      - Theatre Training Final Report, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 474)
      - Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 475)
      - Award Letters, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 476)
      - Final Report, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 477)
      - Letter of Intent, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 478)
      - Revised Budget, 1989-1989 (Box 11, Folder 479)
      - Training Proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 480)
      - Site Visit, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 481)
      - Final Report, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 482 - 483)
      - Theater Magazine Application, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 484)
      - Letter of Intent, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 485)
      - Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 486)
      - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 487)
  - Professional Theatre Companies
    - 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 488)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 489)
    - Site Visit, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 490)
    - Proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 491)
    - Contract and Award Letter, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 492)
    - Revised Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 493)
    - Final Report, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 494)
    - Application Guidelines, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 495)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 496)